[{"body": [{"title": "分类填空", "stem": "天上飞的输入“0”，水里游的输入“1”，地上跑的输入“2”", "titleInfo": [{"type": "fly", "num": 0}, {"type": "swim", "num": 1}, {"type": "run", "num": 2}], "content": [{"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/长颈鹿_L1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜻蜓_F1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/水母_F1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_L1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/小狗_R1.svg", "val": ""}], "type": "au-classify-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [2, 0, 1, 1, 0, 2], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类填空", "stem": "天上飞的输入“0”，水里游的输入“1”，地上跑的输入“2”", "titleInfo": [{"type": "fly", "num": 0}, {"type": "swim", "num": 1}, {"type": "run", "num": 2}], "content": [{"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/6_特殊类别_蝴蝶/蝴蝶_F1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L4.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/长颈鹿_L1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/斑马_L1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/水母_F1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R1.svg", "val": ""}], "type": "au-classify-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [0, 1, 2, 2, 1, 0], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类填空", "stem": "天上飞的输入“0”，水里游的输入“1”，地上跑的输入“2”", "titleInfo": [{"type": "fly", "num": 0}, {"type": "swim", "num": 1}, {"type": "run", "num": 2}], "content": [{"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/猫_L1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L2.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/水母_F1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/6_特殊类别_蝴蝶/蝴蝶_F1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/山羊_R1.svg", "val": ""}], "type": "au-classify-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [2, 1, 0, 1, 0, 2], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类填空", "stem": "天上飞的输入“0”，水里游的输入“1”，地上跑的输入“2”", "titleInfo": [{"type": "fly", "num": 0}, {"type": "swim", "num": 1}, {"type": "run", "num": 2}], "content": [{"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鲸鱼_F1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/斑马_L1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜻蜓_F1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/海豚_L1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/6_特殊类别_蝴蝶/蝴蝶_F1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/狮子_L1.svg", "val": ""}], "type": "au-classify-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [1, 2, 0, 1, 0, 2], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类填空", "stem": "天上飞的输入“0”，水里游的输入“1”，地上跑的输入“2”", "titleInfo": [{"type": "fly", "num": 0}, {"type": "swim", "num": 1}, {"type": "run", "num": 2}], "content": [{"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/水母_F1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/山羊_R1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/牛_L1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/6_特殊类别_蝴蝶/蝴蝶_F1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜻蜓_F1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_R2.svg", "val": ""}], "type": "au-classify-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [1, 2, 2, 0, 0, 1], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类填空", "stem": "天上飞的输入“0”，水里游的输入“1”，地上跑的输入“2”", "titleInfo": [{"type": "fly", "num": 0}, {"type": "swim", "num": 1}, {"type": "run", "num": 2}], "content": [{"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/斑马_L1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L4.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/猪_R1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/6_特殊类别_蝴蝶/蝴蝶_F1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L6.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_L1.svg", "val": ""}], "type": "au-classify-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [2, 1, 2, 0, 1, 0], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类填空", "stem": "天上飞的输入“0”，水里游的输入“1”，地上跑的输入“2”", "titleInfo": [{"type": "fly", "num": 0}, {"type": "swim", "num": 1}, {"type": "run", "num": 2}], "content": [{"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/水母_F1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L2.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/6_特殊类别_蝴蝶/蝴蝶_R1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/小狗_R1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/猫_L1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜜蜂_L1.svg", "val": ""}], "type": "au-classify-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [1, 1, 0, 2, 2, 0], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类填空", "stem": "天上飞的输入“0”，水里游的输入“1”，地上跑的输入“2”", "titleInfo": [{"type": "fly", "num": 0}, {"type": "swim", "num": 1}, {"type": "run", "num": 2}], "content": [{"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/6_特殊类别_蝴蝶/蝴蝶_R1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/猫_L1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/狮子_L1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/6_特殊类别_蝴蝶/蝴蝶_F1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L4.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜜蜂_L1.svg", "val": ""}], "type": "au-classify-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [0, 2, 2, 0, 1, 0], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类填空", "stem": "天上飞的输入“0”，水里游的输入“1”，地上跑的输入“2”", "titleInfo": [{"type": "fly", "num": 0}, {"type": "swim", "num": 1}, {"type": "run", "num": 2}], "content": [{"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/斑马_L1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鲸鱼_F1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L3.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_L1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R5.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/猪_R1.svg", "val": ""}], "type": "au-classify-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [2, 1, 1, 0, 0, 2], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类填空", "stem": "天上飞的输入“0”，水里游的输入“1”，地上跑的输入“2”", "titleInfo": [{"type": "fly", "num": 0}, {"type": "swim", "num": 1}, {"type": "run", "num": 2}], "content": [{"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L6.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/狮子_L1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜻蜓_F1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/小狗_R1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L1.svg", "val": ""}], "type": "au-classify-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [1, 2, 0, 0, 2, 1], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类填空", "stem": "天上飞的输入“0”，水里游的输入“1”，地上跑的输入“2”", "titleInfo": [{"type": "fly", "num": 0}, {"type": "swim", "num": 1}, {"type": "run", "num": 2}], "content": [{"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/海豚_L1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/牛_L1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_L1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_R2.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/绵羊_L1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/6_特殊类别_蝴蝶/蝴蝶_F1.svg", "val": ""}], "type": "au-classify-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [1, 2, 0, 1, 2, 0], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类填空", "stem": "天上飞的输入“0”，水里游的输入“1”，地上跑的输入“2”", "titleInfo": [{"type": "fly", "num": 0}, {"type": "swim", "num": 1}, {"type": "run", "num": 2}], "content": [{"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/海马_L1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/6_特殊类别_蝴蝶/蝴蝶_F1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/山羊_R1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜻蜓_F1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/牛_L1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_R2.svg", "val": ""}], "type": "au-classify-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [1, 0, 2, 0, 2, 1], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类填空", "stem": "天上飞的输入“0”，水里游的输入“1”，地上跑的输入“2”", "titleInfo": [{"type": "fly", "num": 0}, {"type": "swim", "num": 1}, {"type": "run", "num": 2}], "content": [{"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/猫_L1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R5.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L3.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L6.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/长颈鹿_L1.svg", "val": ""}], "type": "au-classify-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [2, 0, 0, 1, 1, 2], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类填空", "stem": "天上飞的输入“0”，水里游的输入“1”，地上跑的输入“2”", "titleInfo": [{"type": "fly", "num": 0}, {"type": "swim", "num": 1}, {"type": "run", "num": 2}], "content": [{"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/小狗_R1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_L1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R5.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/长颈鹿_L1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_R2.svg", "val": ""}], "type": "au-classify-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [1, 2, 0, 0, 2, 1], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类填空", "stem": "天上飞的输入“0”，水里游的输入“1”，地上跑的输入“2”", "titleInfo": [{"type": "fly", "num": 0}, {"type": "swim", "num": 1}, {"type": "run", "num": 2}], "content": [{"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_L1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/狮子_L1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/海豚_L1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/牛_L1.svg", "val": ""}], "type": "au-classify-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [0, 2, 0, 1, 1, 2], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类填空", "stem": "天上飞的输入“0”，水里游的输入“1”，地上跑的输入“2”", "titleInfo": [{"type": "fly", "num": 0}, {"type": "swim", "num": 1}, {"type": "run", "num": 2}], "content": [{"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L6.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/狮子_L1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/长颈鹿_L1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_L1.svg", "val": ""}], "type": "au-classify-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [1, 1, 2, 2, 0, 0], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类填空", "stem": "天上飞的输入“0”，水里游的输入“1”，地上跑的输入“2”", "titleInfo": [{"type": "fly", "num": 0}, {"type": "swim", "num": 1}, {"type": "run", "num": 2}], "content": [{"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜻蜓_F1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/山羊_R1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L6.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L2.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜜蜂_L1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/小狗_R1.svg", "val": ""}], "type": "au-classify-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [0, 2, 1, 1, 0, 2], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类填空", "stem": "天上飞的输入“0”，水里游的输入“1”，地上跑的输入“2”", "titleInfo": [{"type": "fly", "num": 0}, {"type": "swim", "num": 1}, {"type": "run", "num": 2}], "content": [{"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L4.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/长颈鹿_L1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜜蜂_L1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/狮子_L1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鲸鱼_F1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R1.svg", "val": ""}], "type": "au-classify-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [1, 2, 0, 2, 1, 0], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类填空", "stem": "天上飞的输入“0”，水里游的输入“1”，地上跑的输入“2”", "titleInfo": [{"type": "fly", "num": 0}, {"type": "swim", "num": 1}, {"type": "run", "num": 2}], "content": [{"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_R2.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/6_特殊类别_蝴蝶/蝴蝶_R1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜻蜓_F1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_L1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/水母_F1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/小狗_R1.svg", "val": ""}], "type": "au-classify-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类填空", "stem": "天上飞的输入“0”，水里游的输入“1”，地上跑的输入“2”", "titleInfo": [{"type": "fly", "num": 0}, {"type": "swim", "num": 1}, {"type": "run", "num": 2}], "content": [{"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/斑马_L1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/小狗_R1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/6_特殊类别_蝴蝶/蝴蝶_R1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/水母_F1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鲸鱼_F1.svg", "val": ""}], "type": "au-classify-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [0, 2, 2, 0, 1, 1], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类填空", "stem": "天上飞的输入“0”，水里游的输入“1”，地上跑的输入“2”", "titleInfo": [{"type": "fly", "num": 0}, {"type": "swim", "num": 1}, {"type": "run", "num": 2}], "content": [{"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_L1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/斑马_L1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜻蜓_F1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R5.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鲸鱼_F1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/小狗_R1.svg", "val": ""}], "type": "au-classify-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [0, 2, 0, 0, 1, 2], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-05"}]